vinodham.com 2015-09-19

# Latest Film News, Political News, Movie Galleries, Movie Reviews, Photos, Trailers, Box Office & Censor Reports - Vinodham.com

**Disclaimer & Privacy policy:**

Information provided on www.vinodham.com is completely free up to some extent. To avail some of our services you may be asked to provide your Personal information like name, age, gender, contact details so as to contact you. If you want to avail our contact and advertise with us service you will be contacted by the details you provide us. We will not share your personal information to any third parties they will only be used for our internal purposes to serve you better.

**Cookies**

We use cookies which are small files stored on users computer. Cookies can be accessed by the web server or client server which allows the server to deliver a page to a particular user. Persistent cookies will be accessed by our server to ensure optimum experience next time you visit our site and for processes such as saving your username and password till your next sign in. We also use session cookies to stop others to login with the same account simultaneously. We do collect some data regarding user searches, ip address, date and time which are used only for internal processes like website maintenance and visitors log to enhance you with a better and upgraded technology every time. All computers have the ability to accept or decline a cookie automatically. This can be altered manually by going to settings on your browser. If the cookies are disabled you will not be able to view some particular parts of our website. Google and other third party advertisers access your cookies to deliver advertisements on the page you visit tailor made according to your search criteria and other aspects.

**Third Party Links and Downloads**

Third party links of several website are found on our website we do not hold any responsibility or liability to their policies as they have their own Legal policies. We do not share your information to any third parties except in some cases where legal authorities request us to provide some information regarding misuse and damage to our behold laws and property. We will only disclose your geographical data such as place and time of visiting the site but not your email id and personal information. Download links are provided by third party providers who display content in their website and all the legal proceedings are sole responsible of the particular websites.

**Note**

Privacy Policy and Disclaimer may be changed according to the requirements and such changes will surely be displayed or will make into your notice before implementing. Although some modifications will be done without any prior notice.
